{
  "LevelId": 34,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 346,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "HASSLE",
      "question": "another word for \"a bothersome or annoying situation\""
    },
    {
      "id": 347,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "INSECT",
      "question": "tiny creature with six legs is often associated with buzzing sounds"
    },
    {
      "id": 348,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CANCER",
      "question": "disease characterized by the uncontrolled growth and spread of abnormal cells in the body"
    },
    {
      "id": 349,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "HORROR",
      "question": "literature, film, or entertainment aims to evoke fear, dread, and a sense of terror in its audience"
    },
    {
      "id": 350,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "SCREEN",
      "question": "electronic device component serves as a visual display,"
    },
    {
      "id": 351,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CATTLE",
      "question": "domesticated animals are commonly raised for meat, milk,"
    },
    {
      "id": 352,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "SAFARI",
      "question": "type of adventurous journey, often associated with wildlife viewing and exploration,"
    },
    {
      "id": 353,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "FLORAL",
      "question": "term is used to describe things related to flowers or plants"
    },
    {
      "id": 354,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CLAYED",
      "question": "term describes an object or surface covered with a malleable substance"
    },
    {
      "id": 355,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "SECRETARY",
      "question": "office setting, what role is typically responsible for administrative tasks, organizing schedules,"
    }
  ]
}